savieo.com 2018-09-02

# Privacy Policy · Savieo · Your #1 tool for saving videos and tracks off the open web

### Introduction

Savieo.com, ("we" or "us") values its visitors' privacy. This privacy policy is effective as of the date displayed at the bottom of this page; it summarizes what information we might collect from a registered user or other visitor ("you"), and what we will and will not do with it. 

Please note that this privacy policy does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that Savieo.com does not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by Savieo.com. If you visit a Web site that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information. 

### What we do with your personally identifiable information

It is always up to you whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us, although if you elect not to do so, we reserve the right not to register you as a user or provide you with any products or services. "Personally identifiable information" (PII) means information that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as, for example: 

  * email address, country and prefered language
  * any account-preference information you provide us
  * your computer's domain name and IP address, indicating where your computer is located on the Internet

If you do provide personally identifiable information to us, either directly or through a third party api or other business partner, we will: 

  * not sell or rent it to a third party without your permission - although unless you opt out (see below), we may use your contact information to provide you with information we believe you need to know or may find useful, such as (for example) news about our services and products and modifications to the service
  * take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction
  * not use or disclose the information except:
    * as necessary to provide services or products you have ordered, such as (for example) by providing it to a carrier to deliver products you have ordered
    * in other ways described in this privacy policy or to which you have otherwise consented
    * in the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity cannot reasonably be determined (for example, statistical compilations)
    * as required by law, for example, in response to a subpoena or search warrant
    * to outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential
    * as necessary to protect the rights, safety, or property of Savieo.com, its users, or others; this may include (for example) exchanging information with other pages for fraud protection and/or risk reduction

### Other information we collect

We may collect other information that cannot be readily used to identify you, such as (for example) the domain name and IP address of your computer. We may use this information, individually or in the aggregate, for technical administration of our Web site(s); research and development; customer and account administration; and to help us focus our marketing efforts more precisely. 

### Cookies

Savieo.com does not use or store any "cookies". 

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies to administer and provide the Savieo.com services on our behalf (including, without limitation, bill and credit card payment processing, maintenance, administration, support, hosting and database management services, email and sms providers). These third parties may have access to your PII only to perform these tasks on our behalf in accordance with this Privacy Policy and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. 

### Business Transfers

Savieo.com may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its business or assets, including your personal information, in connection with a business deal (or potential business deal) such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy, in which case we will require the recipient to honor this Privacy Policy. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that any acquirer or successor of Savieo.com or its assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site or Service of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

### Your privacy responsibilities

To help protect your privacy, be sure: 

  * to take customary precautions to guard against "malware" (viruses, Trojan horses, bots, etc.), for example by installing and updating suitable anti-virus software

### Safe Harbor Compliance Statement

Savieo.com complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Savieo.com has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit [www.export.gov/safeharbor](https://www.export.gov/safeharbor). 

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Savieo.com commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Savieo.com by emailing [mail@savieo.com](mailto:mail@savieo.com). 

Savieo.com has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Savieo.com, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](https://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint. 

### Notice to European Union users

Savieo.com's operations are located primarily in the United States. If you provide information to us, the information will be transferred out of the European Union (EU) to the United States. By providing personal information to us, you are consenting to its storage and use as described herein. 

### Information collected from children

You must be at least 13 years old to use Savieo.com's Web application(s) and/or service(s). We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13. (See the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.) 

### Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy as we deem necessary or appropriate because of legal compliance requirements or changes in our business practices. We will endeavor to notify you, by email if available or via notice on our website, of any material change to how we will use personally identifiable information. 

### Questions or comments?

If you have questions or comments about Savieo.com's privacy policy, send an email to [mail@savieo.com](mailto:mail@savieo.com). 

Last Updated: July 1st, 2016
